myron.com 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy | Myron Promotional Products & Gifts

**Last Updated: July 13, 2012**

This Privacy Policy sets forth the policies of Myron Corp. (“Myron,” “we,” “us” or “our”), located in the United States, with respect to personal information that is collected from Registered Users of the Site.  All capitalized terms not defined herein shall have the meaning attributed to them in the Terms of Use of the Site. 

**By voluntarily providing us with your personal information you expressly consent to the collection and processing by Myron of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.**

If you provide, or authorize the provision of your personal information to this Site, you acknowledge and expressly agree that such personal information may be transferred, for the purposes as defined in this Privacy Policy, from your current location to the offices and servers of Myron and the authorized third parties (the “Third Parties”) referred to herein located in countries outside of the United States, which may have different standards of data protection; your personal information will only ever be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy however).

We collect and process your personal information when you voluntarily choose to become a Registered User and/or purchase Products and/or Services via the Site. We also collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you browse the Site as a User. 

The following personal information will be collected and processed: professional e-mail address, professional phone number, professional address, title, primary contact person and, where applicable, a description of your preferences for Products and/or Services. If your purchase Products and/or Services via the Site, we will also request that your provide information for payment and billing purposes such as credit card information and billing address.

## Other data

**_Passively-collected information:_** When you interact with Myron through the Site, we receive and store certain non-personally identifiable information. Such information, which is collected passively using various technologies, cannot presently be used to specifically identify you. Myron may store such information itself or it may be included in databases owned and maintained by Myron’ affiliates, agents, or service providers. This Site may use such information and pool it with other information to track, for example, the total number of visitors to our Site, the number of visitors to each page of our Site, and the domain names of our visitors’ Internet service providers. It is important to note that no personal information is available or used in this process.

**_Aggregated personal information:_** In an ongoing effort to better understand our Registered Users, Myron might analyze the personal information that is provided to the Site in aggregate form. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. Myron may share this aggregate data with other Registered Users, its affiliates, agents, and business partners. We may also disclose aggregated User statistics in order to describe our business, including our Products and Services, to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**_Cookies:_ **In operating the Site, we may use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Site gives to your computer when you access a web site. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Site and help us analyze Site usage more accurately. In all cases in which we use cookies, we will not collect personal information except with your permission. On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off. We recommend that you leave cookies turned on because they allow you to take advantage of some of the Site’s features. 

## How we use personal information

Myron uses the personal information you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. We will use the personal information you input during the registration process to administer access to the Site, to respond to submissions made to the Site, to fulfill orders for Products and/or Services, and to collect payment. We may use your personal information to send you a newsletter or email messages with updates and notices concerning new Products and Services available via the Site or other distribution channels, and, if you opt-in during registration, we will also alert you to third-party products and services that we believe would be of interest to you. Myron will also use your personal information and certain non-personally identifiable information collected through the Site to help us improve the Content and functionality of the Site, to better understand the Registered Users of our Site, and to improve our offerings. Your credit card information is not shared with third parties except to designated third-party service providers for purposes of processing orders. With the exception of credit card information, Myron may (subject to your option to opt-out of such activities at registration) share, rent, trade, or sell personal information (except for phone numbers and e-mail addresses), to or with other Registered Users, its affiliates, agents, business partners, market analysts, advertisers, sponsors, and to any other Third Parties for marketing and other purposes.

If Myron intends on using any personal information in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to or at the time at which the personal information is collected.

## How we share the information that we receive

We may share your personal information with **Third Parties** including, but not limited to, the following: Agents, Consultants, and related Third Parties. Myron, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples include mailing information, maintaining databases, and processing payments. When we employ another company to perform a function of this nature, we provide them only with the information that they need to perform their specific function, and we select companies that provide sufficient guarantees of confidentiality and security. We ensure that the company will act only on our instructions and will have appropriate technical and organizational measures to protect your personal information.

**Legal requirements:** Myron may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) comply with a legal obligation, (b) protect and defend the rights or property of Myron, (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Site or the public, or (d) protect against legal liability.

**Business transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event, personal information may be part of the transferred assets.

**What are your choices  
**As outlined in this Privacy Policy, you can always choose not to provide your personal information to the Site, however doing so may prevent you from obtaining certain information or using other valuable features of the Site. During the registration process for Registered Users, our Site provides an opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Myron and/or Third Parties.

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads and/or collect certain information when you visit our website. These companies may use cookies or web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information such as IP Address, pages viewed, and if a conversion occurred during your visit to this website in order to help show advertisements on other websites likely to be more interesting to you. To learn more about this “behavioral advertising” practice or to opt-out of this use of your anonymous information, you can visit [www.networkadvertising.org](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

## How to opt-out of marketing newsletters and special offer promotions

From time to time, we may send you marketing and special offer emails that may interest you. If you do not wish to receive these emails you may choose to "opt-out" by any of the following methods:

a)The fastest and easiest way to opt-out of our emails is to click on the "Unsubscribe" link found at the bottom of our marketing emails.

b)You can also unsubscribe by unchecking the "Newsletter Status" box found under "My Profile" in the "My Account" section.

c)Call us at 1-877-803-3358 or write to [service@myron.com](mailto:service@myron.com) requesting we remove your name from our mailing lists. Please note that we will use all our reasonable efforts to do so in a timely fashion. 

## Safe Harbor Privacy Principles

Myron Corp. complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  Myron Corp. has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view Myron Corp.'s certification, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>.

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Myron commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information.  European Union or Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact Myron as described below in the How To Contact Us section.

Myron has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Myron, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site at [www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints](http://www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints) for more information and to file a complaint.

## Links to other web sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site and not to any Third-Party Sites or any Other Myron Sites. We suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy, security, and data collection and distribution policies.

## Unsolicited information

This Privacy Policy shall not apply to any Unsolicited Information you provide to the Site to the extent that the Unsolicited Information does not contain any personal information.

## Security

We take commercially reasonable steps to protect personal information provided to the Site and to protect such information from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. We use industry-standard SSL (“Secure Socket Layer”) encryption technology, a secure server, and other physical and procedural safeguards to protect the security of your personal information. Please understand, however, that no security system is impenetrable. We cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that the personal information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to and from us over the Internet. In particular, e-mail sent to or from the Site may not be secure, and you should therefore take special care in deciding what information you send to us via e-mail. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any personal information to Myron or to any other party via the Internet.

## Other terms and conditions

Your access to and use of this Site is subject to the Terms of Use which is hereby incorporated by reference.

## Changes to the Privacy Policy

Myron reserves the right to amend this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. If you use the Site after this Privacy Policy has been posted, you will be deemed to have agreed to this Privacy Policy. 

Notice to Registered Users: If you are a Registered User, please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page. Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date. If you use this Site or the Services after we post changes to the Policy, you will be bound by the revised Policy.

Notice to Users: If you are not a Registered User, you should check the Privacy Policy each time you use the Site to determine if any changes have been made. If you use the Site after the amended Privacy Policy has been posted, you will be deemed to have agreed to the amended Privacy Policy.

## Change your Registered User profile

You may view and correct your personal information by accessing the Registered User link on the header of the Site. Please note that you must log in with your private Sign-In Name, Password, and Unique Identifiers to access and/or your Registered User Profile.

## Right to access, modify, and oppose to the processing of your data

You have the ability to access your personal information, rectify and correct or delete inaccurate, incomplete, equivocal, expired Data as well as the ability to object to the processing of your personal information, for legitimate purposes. To exercise any of these rights, please contact Myron in the manner described below.

## How to contact us

Please feel free to contact us if you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the information practices of Myron with respect to personal information collected and processed from this Site.

You may contact us as follows:

  * E-mail: [service@myron.com](mailto:service@myron.com)

  * Regular Mail:   
Myron Corp.   
205 Maywood Avenue   
Maywood, NJ 07607 

  * Phone: 201-843-6796
